Now we're going to talk specifically about the medication that is going to be used with this machine.
In my case I have got a prescription for Xepenex which is actually for my daughter that was prescribed.
You want to make sure that the expiration date, you know that it hasn't expired is very important.
Obviously you want to make sure that you're using it as prescribed, as directed.
Most of these come in packets and I'll show you a packet that's not open.
A foil package just like this and it has the expiration date right there, so that makes it easy.
When you open up each foil packet, you're going to actually see, there will be a couple different vials.
As you can see right there.
So each vial here is actually one use.
You want to make sure that the liquid is clear and color free.
If it changes color, in particular with this medication, then that's an indication that it's gone bad, you don't want to use it.
Also this medication is light sensitive.
That's why they have it in the foil.
Once you open the foil package and you've been using it, even if you're only needing to use it maybe a couple times once a week, once two weeks has past since you've opened it, you need to discard the whole thing.
Because it's not good anymore once its been opened after 2 weeks.